Sarah Crosby

Experienced web designer with a keen eye for design, excellent visual design skills and solid technical know-how. Ability to work collaboratively in an agile environment to translate high level requirements into intuitive design.

Boston, MA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Sarah-Crosby/e4a4eeddcb49e79a

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Designer

Skillsoft/Books24x7 - Norwood, MA - June 2002 to April 2016

In my most recent position at Skillsoft, the Global Leader in eLearning, I was the Web Designer on the Books24x7 Engineering team. In my role I was the creative lead for the Books24x7 product. I designed and redesigned many aspects of the product including the social networking feature, HTML emails, search, icon creation, dynamic features, and websites for customer events to name a few. I created mock-ups, HTML, CSS and was involved in every step of the development process from concept to launch. I was also a member of the UX Team for Skillsoft where I participated in cross functional global teams to address issues, create new features and redesign features of the product. I provided mockups, graphics, HTML and provided CSS consultation and guidance.

Web Site Builder, Web Solutions Group

Genuity - Cambridge, MA - November 2001 to May 2002

Maintained and updated corporate website. Created HTML templates for marketing campaign. Used Homesite as a web editor.

Web Designer

Wave Technologies/Thomson Learning - Boston, MA - October 2000 to April 2001

At Wave Technologies I was the Web Designer on the Development team. I led the design effort as I artfully created a prototype that entailed my original design, layout, graphics and navigation features. I worked closely with the developers as we converted my html pages to ColdFusion pages that displayed dynamic web content. I received excellent feedback regarding my clean and simple design.

EDUCATION

BA in English Major/French Minor

University of Massachusetts - Amherst, MA

Certificate in Web Design

Boston University - Boston, MA

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Agile/Scrum Environment, JQuery, Javascript, Responsive Web Design

LINKS

http://www.sarahcrosby.com

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Currently I am working on a freelance project for Corfinio, Italian Grill Restaurant. I am designing the web site using PhotoShop and DreamWeaver. I am incorporating CSS, JQuery, and Responsive design as well. Phase one of the project is finished. The site is published. See it @ www.corfinioeaston.com. Phase two will involve incorporating Google Analytics, an image carousel, and more SEO options.